> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 还有一件事，现在我们有照片，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So one more thing,
now we have photos,
我们知道的是一系列的照片串行吗
which we know is going to be
an array of photo strings, okay?
现在，我们只需执行此 handleIndexClick 函数。
Now we just have to make this
handleIndexClick function.
> > Brian Holt: 那么，让我们先这样做吧，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So, let's go ahead and
do it this way first,
我们先把它建错了然后我们再教你怎么做
we're gonna build it wrong first and
then we'll show you how to make it right.
>> Brian Holt: 好， handleIndexClick，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, handleIndexClick,
这件事将会发生在某种形式上
this is gonna take in an event
of some sort like this.
>> Brian Holt: 在此处，我们只想调用 this.setstate ，并激活
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And here we just wanna
call this.setstate, with active
成为 event.target.dataset.index >> Brian Holt: 因此
being the event.target.dataset.index
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
这件事有两个问题让我们来谈谈
there's two things wrong with this,
let's talk about both of them.
第一个，如果你之前从未见过数据集，
The first one,
if you've never seen dataset before,
这不是一个反应 API ，这是一个愚蠢的 API，对吧 ?
this is not a react API,
this is a dumb API, right?
数据集允许您获取数据中的两个内容，
And dataset allows you to get
two things that are on the data,
在每个音符标记上，对吗 ?
on the each note tag, right?
所以我就有了这个图像标签，我有这个数据索引。
So I had this image tag here right,
and I had this data index.
这就是我们所说的数据集，让我们关闭你。
So this dataset that we're referring to,
let's close you.
好了好了
[BLANK AUDIO] There we go.
所以数据集索引，就会引用此处的任何内容，对吧 ?
So dataset index, that's going to
refer to whatever is here, right?
那里会有 0， 1， 2， 3 和 4 。
So it'll have zero, one, two,
three and four in there.
有道理吗
That make sense?
但我们要牢记的是积极的需要是一个数字因为我们
But the thing to keep in mind here is
active needs to be a number because we're
在这里做个数字对吧
using as a number down here, right?
任何来自蠢蛋的反应都是一串字符串
Anything that comes react from the dumb
is always gonna be a string, so
我们得把这个转换成一个数字我们得把这个变成一个数字
we need to convert this into a number,
we need to coerce this into a number.
有几种方法可以做到这一点。
There's a number of ways of doing this.
你可以做 parseInt 之类的，也可以说 " Plus" 。
You could do parseInt or something
like that, or you can just say Plus.
如果你把那个叫一元加的东西放在那儿
If you put what's call
the unary plus right there,
把它变成一个数字
that will turn it into a number.
>> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
所以这个问题号就解决了。
So that's problem number one solved.
我说过这个，对不起，在那里，那是第三个问题。
And I said this, sorry, this.setState
right there, that's a third problem.
[ LAUGH] This.setState。
[LAUGH] This.setState.
我们在这里的另一个问题是什么呢 ?
The other problem that we
have here is what is this?
所以如果我在这里叫它作为一个活动的听众
So, if I'm calling it as
an event listener down here,
你觉得这会是什么
what do you think this is gonna be here?
>> 演讲者 2: 下载?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Download?
> > Brian Holt: 我认为没什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I think it's nothing.
我觉得是没有定义的
I think it's undefined.
你在正确的轨道上是不正确的对吧
You're on the right track
that it's not correct, right?
>> Brian Holt: 我们需要它作为组件，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We need it
to be the component, right?
我们需要做轮播组件因为我们想叫一个 setState on
We need it be the carousel component
because we wanna call a setState on
这不是窗户或者我觉得它是未定义的
the carousel component, and this is
either Window or I think it's undefined.
我认为反应是没有定义的。
I think react makes it undefined.
不管你想做什么都不是你想要的
Regardless, it's not
what you want it to be.
那么，我要怎么做呢 ?
So how would I make this correct?
这里有两种方法我都给你们看
There's two methodologies here,
I'll show you both of them.
如果我在这里有个施工人员就说我有了道具 ( 道具)
If I had a constructor up here, so
just say I had constructor (props), and
你不用复印这个，我就给你看这个，超级(道具)。
you don't have to copy this one, I'm
just showing you this one, super(props).
如果你没有公共课你可以在这里做什么
What you could do here if
you don't have public class
在您的项目中启用了许多您将不会使用的属性。
properties enabled in your project
which many of you will not.
你可以进来然后
You can come in here and put,
this.handleIndexClick=this.handleIndexCli- ckbind(此)。
this.handleIndexClick=this.handleIndexCli-
ck.bind(this).
这看起来太荒谬了吧
This looks ridiculous, right?
但这到底是干什么的，对吗 ?
But what is this actually doing, right?
它将 handleIndexClick 的上下文绑定为 Carousel，
It's binding the context of
handleIndexClick to be Carousel,
因为我们知道这在建造者里会有什么保证
because we know what this is inside
the constructor would guarantee it's gonna
是正确的环境，对吧 ?
be the correct context, right?
因此，这意味着可以调用 handleIndexClick ，并且
So this means that handleIndexClick
can then be called, and
这个永远是对的，对，所以这个工作。
this will always be correct,
right, so this works.
虽然这样做有更容易的方法
There's an even easier way to do this,
though,
如果您有这样的公共类属性。
if you have public class
properties like this.
>> Brian Holt: 我可以转至- >> Brian Holt: 一个箭头函数。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I can just turn this into-
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: An arrow function.
> > Brian Holt: 现在又正确了，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now it's correct again,
right?
因为我们谈到了箭的功能，对，他们是不创造新的背景的，
Because we talked about arrow functions,
right, they don't create new context when
他们被引到了这意味着它在词法上
they're invoked,
which means that it gets it lexically,
这在技术上并不正确，但实际上是正确的，对吧 ?
which is not actually technically correct
but effectively is correct, right?
所以你写的时候就决定了，对，所以
So this is determined when you write it,
right, so
这一切就会发生在任何地方
this is going to be
wherever it was written.
但如果我在这里称为这样的功能，对吗 ?
Whereas if I you call a function
like this function here, right?
这将会是它是否被调用现在意识到这可能不是一种
It's going to be whether it's invoked,
now recognize it's probably not a kind of
有一个奇怪的区分，但就足以说，这将是正确的
an odd distinction to make but suffice
to say, this will have the correct this
因为此事件侦听器不会创建新的上下文。
because this event listener's
not gonna create a new context.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 所以我要给你一个大拇指规则
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I'm gonna give you
just kind of a rule of thumb here.
只要你把职能转移到孩子的时候，对吧 ?
Whenever you are passing functions
down into children, right?
或者每当你在做活动听众的时候
Or whenever you're doing event listeners,
使用箭头函数， >> Brian Holt: 因为这将保证
use an arrow function,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Because that will guarantee
这才是正确的
what this is to be is correct.
就像我们 componentDidMount 里的告示
Like notice here in our componentDidMount
in details and this one, notice that
我们不需要为 componentDidMount 的 this.setState 执行任何魔法
we didn't have to do any magic for
this.setState for componentDidMount that's
因为 componentDidMount，我们已经知道它将具有正确的上下文。
because componentDidMount, we already
know it's gonna have the correct context.
与呈现方式相同，呈现始终具有相同的正确上下文。
Same thing with render, render is always
gonna have the same correct context.
所以它真的只是个事件的听众
So it's really just event listeners and
你要传递给孩子们的功能就是这样
functions that you're passing
into children, that's it.